Jeremy what's happening?
杰里米发生了什么？
I, I actually dont know!!
我 我真的不知道   这太奇怪了
This is so bizzare. cloudy weather appeared suddenly.
这真是太奇怪了 阴天突然出现
Jeremy! something is not right!
杰里米 情况不对
What should we do Einstein? Destroy the whole thing up?
我们应该怎么做 爱因斯坦？把这一切都毁掉吗？
Oh no! XANA's starting to control the weather all over the world.
哦 不 XANA开始控制全世界的天气了
This is incredible.
这真是不可思议
A world wide attack? How is even be that's even possible.
世界范围的攻击？这怎么可能呢
We have to stop this. XANA is gain more power over time.
我们必须要阻止这一切 随着时间的推移 XANA正在获得更多的力量
We can do anything to stop it.
我们可以做任何事情来阻止它
What are you planning to doing? ideas?
你打算怎么做？
I dont know.
我不知道
But XANA is so powerful.
但XANA是如此强大
Breaking news line.
爆炸性新闻线
Hello everyone I'm Martha.
大家好 我是玛莎
And thank you so much for choosing channel 3 for your news.
非常感谢您选择第三频道的新闻
Today something different happen worldwide.
今天全世界发生了一些不同的事情
Recently a cloudy weather appeared all over the world.
最近 世界各地都出现了多云的天气
And rain says it's everywhere as well.
雨说它也是到处都是
No one knows how this happened so suddenly.
没有人知道这一切是如何突然发生的
Our country leaders wants people to be relaxed.
我们的国家领导人希望人们能够放松警惕
But everyone should be careful against flood.
但是每个人都应该小心防范洪水
We're now connected to John.
我们现在和约翰联系上了
Hello Martha I am in the city park.
你好 玛莎 我在城市公园里
And we have rain in here too.
我们这里也有雨
Rain started in Turkey, Egypt, Japan, the United States of America,
土耳其、埃及、日本、美国都开始下雨
India, Greek, Romania, Italy, Sweden, Russia, Brazil,
印度 希腊 罗马尼亚 意大利 瑞典 俄罗斯 巴西
German, Syria, China, South and North Korea,
德国、叙利亚、中国、南韩和北韩
Australia, Canada, Spain, Portugal and other countries
澳大利亚、加拿大、西班牙、葡萄牙和其他国家
and oh my god! There's thunder everywhere. Ahhh!!!
而我的天啊 到处都有雷声 啊
John? Can you hear me? John?
约翰？你能听到我吗？约翰？
Please everyone be carefull about the danger.
请大家注意这个危险
It might be turn into disaster.
它可能会变成灾难
I am Martha. Still have a nice day. Please be carefull.
我是玛莎 祝你有一个愉快的一天 请注意安全
This is not good! This is awful. This is awful.
这不是好事 这是可怕的 这是可怕的
Lyoko Warriors do you read me?
莱科勇士们 你们能听到我吗？
Yumi! Go and warn the principal.
Yumi! 去警告校长
Others get back to the factory right now! XANA can attack!
其他人马上回工厂去 XANA可以攻击!
With the costume.
用服装
Oh don't worry about it.
哦 不用担心
We can do a return to the past in no time.
我们可以马上做一个回到过去
I wonder how Sissi would react to see me like this.
我想知道茜茜看到我这个样子会有什么反应
Okay Franz we are coming to the factory.
好了 弗兰茨 我们要去工厂了
Great because I have a surprise for you all so hurry up.
很好 因为我有一个惊喜给你们 所以要快点
I'm going to program your vehicles as you can use them in the real world.
我要对你们的车辆进行编程 因为你们可以在现实世界中使用它们
What? That's impossible Einstein.
什么？那是不可能的 爱因斯坦
You will see thats actually possible.
你会看到这实际上是可能的
Just be ready everyone.
只要大家做好准备
All systems are operational, ready and online.
所有的系统都在运行 准备好了 并且在线
Okay! here we go!
好了 我们开始吧
My beatifull Overboard! I cant believe this!
我的胜利落水了! 我无法相信这一点
I just want to say something to you both!
我只想对你们俩说几句话
I love you two so much!
我非常爱你们两个
I can kiss both of you right now!
我现在就可以亲吻你们两个
I always wanted to try this! Oh! Thank you so much!
我一直想试试这个! 哦 非常感谢你们!
Wohooo!!! Hahaha.
呜呜呜    哈哈哈
This is awesome!
这真是太棒了!
And I thought Lyoko couldn't get better!
我还以为Lyoko不能再好了!
I am so high! literally!!
我太高兴了 真的 !
Okay I am going to talk with the principle!
好了 我要去和校长谈谈!
See you soon.
再见
Hello Sissi!
你好 Sissi!
Miss me?
想我吗？
She will never get over this!
她将永远不会忘记这一切
Jeremy! We are heading to the factory.
杰里米 我们要去工厂了
Okay Aelita, be fast! hurry!
好的Aelita 要快 快点
I'm here. I'm going inside right now.
我在这里 我现在要进去了
What the hell?
搞什么鬼？
What was that?
那是什么？
What is that? What the f-
那是什么？这到底是...
Jeremie we need to protect the factory against the XANA attack and hurry.
杰雷米... ...我们需要保护工厂不受XANA的攻击 而且要快
What should we do?
我们应该怎么做？
We will use Aelita's creativity power of course
我们当然要使用艾莉塔的创造力了
My powers? For what?
我的能力？用来做什么？
We need to create some sort of shield against flood Aelita.
我们需要制造一些防护罩来抵御洪水 Aelita
Okay father we are almost there.
好的 父亲 我们快到了
I need to talk with principle!
我需要和原则谈谈
Miss Ishiyama? Is that you?
石山小姐？是你吗？
Yes and I need to talk with the principal, right now.
是的 我需要和校长谈谈 就现在
I am so disappointed at you, Yumi.
我对你太失望了 尤美
You should know by now that you can't walk in Kadic with those type of clothes.
你现在应该知道 你不能穿着这种衣服在卡迪克走动
Go change right now!
现在就去换衣服吧
What's this noise all about? Miss Ishiyama?
这些噪音是怎么回事？石山小姐？
What's the meaning of this?
这到底是什么意思？
She apparently wants to talk with you, Mr. Demas.
她显然想和你谈谈 德马斯先生
Yes I do. It's an emergency Mr. Delmas. Please.
是的 我想 这是一个紧急情况 德玛斯先生 请说
Emergency you say?
你说紧急情况？
Okay okay you can come in hurry up.
好吧好吧 你可以进来了 快点
I want to know what type of emergencies brings you here like this.
我想知道是什么紧急情况让你来这里的
It's the rain! We should evacuate the school right away.
是雨 我们应该马上疏散学校
I can't believe this. This must be a protocol joke.
我无法相信这一点 这一定是一个协议的笑话
You're seriously here like that because of the rain Miss Ishiyama!
你真的是因为下雨才来的吗 石山小姐!
Aghh! This is not an ordinary rain. Why don't you listen to me.
Aghh! 这不是一场普通的雨 你为什么不听我说
What? How dare you.
什么 你怎么敢这么说
Please moderate your tone right here.
请你在这里缓和一下你的语气
I'm not sure yourclassmates are something like that.
我不知道你的同学们是什么样的人
You will show me respect!
你要对我表示尊重
Yeah! and if you don't do anything my classmates will be in danger.
是的 如果你不做什么 我的同学就会有危险
The whole school. Your Sissi. Please listen to me.
整个学校 你的西西 请听我说
No one is in danger. You should relax, Miss Ishiyama.
没有人有危险 你应该放松 石山小姐
Okay I will evacuate the school as soon as possible I can!
好吧 我会尽快疏散学校 我可以
Aelita! It's you! It's really you.
艾莉塔 是你 真的是你
That's amazing! You look so beatiful.
真了不起 你看起来真漂亮
Yes, Jeremy, it's me but I am not real.
是的 杰里米 这是我 但我不是真的
Don't forget that.
不要忘记这一点
There is no time for that.
现在没有时间了
We need to create a shield right now!
我们现在就需要建立一个防护罩!
Okay father.
好的 父亲
I'm starting. Don't worry.
我开始了 别担心
It will just take a second.
这只需要一秒钟